<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Introduction on Showcase Template</title><link>https://xabelian.github.io/VisualComputing/</link><description>Recent content in Introduction on Showcase Template</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://xabelian.github.io/VisualComputing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Creating a New Theme</title><link>https://xabelian.github.io/VisualComputing/posts/creating-a-new-theme/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://xabelian.github.io/VisualComputing/posts/creating-a-new-theme/</guid><description>Introduction # This tutorial will show you how to create a simple theme in Hugo. I assume that you are familiar with HTML, the bash command line, and that you are comfortable using Markdown to format content. I&amp;rsquo;ll explain how Hugo uses templates and how you can organize your templates to create a theme. I won&amp;rsquo;t cover using CSS to style your theme.
We&amp;rsquo;ll start with creating a new site with a very basic template.</description></item><item><title>Migrate to Hugo from Jekyll</title><link>https://xabelian.github.io/VisualComputing/posts/migrate-from-jekyll/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://xabelian.github.io/VisualComputing/posts/migrate-from-jekyll/</guid><description>Move static content to static # Jekyll has a rule that any directory not starting with _ will be copied as-is to the _site output. Hugo keeps all static content under static. You should therefore move it all there. With Jekyll, something that looked like
▾ &amp;lt;root&amp;gt;/ ▾ images/ logo.png should become
▾ &amp;lt;root&amp;gt;/ ▾ static/ ▾ images/ logo.png Additionally, you&amp;rsquo;ll want any files that should reside at the root (such as CNAME) to be moved to static.</description></item><item><title>(Hu)go Template Primer</title><link>https://xabelian.github.io/VisualComputing/posts/goisforlovers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://xabelian.github.io/VisualComputing/posts/goisforlovers/</guid><description>Hugo uses the excellent Go html/template library for its template engine. It is an extremely lightweight engine that provides a very small amount of logic. In our experience that it is just the right amount of logic to be able to create a good static website. If you have used other template systems from different languages or frameworks you will find a lot of similarities in Go templates.
This document is a brief primer on using Go templates.</description></item><item><title>Getting Started with Hugo</title><link>https://xabelian.github.io/VisualComputing/posts/hugoisforlovers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://xabelian.github.io/VisualComputing/posts/hugoisforlovers/</guid><description>Step 1. Install Hugo # Go to Hugo releases and download the appropriate version for your OS and architecture.
Save it somewhere specific as we will be using it in the next step.
More complete instructions are available at Install Hugo
Step 2. Build the Docs # Hugo has its own example site which happens to also be the documentation site you are reading right now.
Follow the following steps:</description></item><item><title/><link>https://xabelian.github.io/VisualComputing/docs/Image-Color-Analysis/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://xabelian.github.io/VisualComputing/docs/Image-Color-Analysis/</guid><description>La computación visual en ayuda de personas con Daltonismo # Introduccion # El daltonismo es la incapacidad para ver algunos colores en la forma normal.
Este ocurre cuando hay un problema con los pigmentos en ciertas células nerviosas del ojo que perciben el color. Estas células se llaman conos y se encuentran en la capa de tejido sensible a la luz que recubre la parte posterior del ojo, llamada la retina.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://xabelian.github.io/VisualComputing/docs/Team-Members/Camilo/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://xabelian.github.io/VisualComputing/docs/Team-Members/Camilo/</guid><description>Info de Camilo #</description></item><item><title/><link>https://xabelian.github.io/VisualComputing/docs/Team-Members/Nicolas/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://xabelian.github.io/VisualComputing/docs/Team-Members/Nicolas/</guid><description>Info de Nicolás #</description></item><item><title/><link>https://xabelian.github.io/VisualComputing/docs/Team-Members/Sergio/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://xabelian.github.io/VisualComputing/docs/Team-Members/Sergio/</guid><description>Sergio Nicolás Rivera # Bio # Mi nombre es Sergio Nicolás Rivera, estudiante de último semestre de Ingenieria de Sistemas y Computación en la Universidad Nacional de Colombia. Desde hace 7 años me desempeñé como analista de calidad en IBM de Colombia trabajado en distintos proyectos, principalmente relacionados con la banca. Desde hace 1 año soy especialista en automatización de pruebas en Globant.
Interests # Desde mi profesión, mi principal interes es la automatización de pruebas principalmente con la herramienta Tosca de la casa Triscentis, asi como por medio de frameworks como Selenium o Jmeter.</description></item></channel></rss>